(Transcribed by TurboScribe.ai. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) When the world was bright and wide, you
were joy right by my side.
Tiny footsteps, cheerful cheers, you wiped away my
little fears.
Through every laugh and every cry, you gave
me love, you gave me time.
In your arms I found my place, sunshine
smiling on your face.
You're the whisper in my joy, the light
in every starry sky.
Oh mother, your hands are my hope, wherever
I wander I'm never alone.
Your love is a river that joyfully flows,
a garden of dreams where my whole life
grows.
If I rise it's because you believe, every
hope in my heart you can see.
Oh mother, no words can say, how I
thank you this Mother's Day.
You turned your strength into my smile,
walked ten thousand blissful miles.
Late night stories, loving eyes, joyful tears behind
caring eyes.
Every lesson softly told, more precious now than
crowns of gold.
Your gentle voice lights up my way, guiding
every cheerful day.
You're the anchor in the bend gently.
Your hands are my hope, wherever I wander
I'm never alone.
Your love is a river that joyfully flows,
a garden of dreams where my whole life
grows.
If I rise it's because you believe, every
hope in my heart you can see.
Oh mother, no words can say, how I
thank you this Mother's Day.
If I could it still would match all
you do, every heart beat joyfully pray.
Oh, your hands are my hope, your love
is the joy I've always known.
Through every season come what may, I'll carry
your love every day.
Forever thankful, forever true, the best of me
comes you see.
I love you more, this Mother's Day.