When the world was bright and wide,
you were joy right by my side.
Tiny footsteps, share for cheers.
You wiped away my little fears.
Through every laugh and every climb,
you gave me love, you gave me time.
In your arms, I found my place.
Sunshine smiling on your face.
You're the whisper in my joy,
the light in every starry sky.
Oh, mother, your hands are my home.
Wherever I wander, I'm never alone.
Your love is a river that joyfully flows,
a garden of dreams where
my whole life grows.
If I rise, it's because you believe.
Every hope in my heart you can see.
Oh, mother, no words can say.
How I thank you this mother's day.
You turned your strength into my smile.
Walk 10,000 blissful miles.
Late night's stories, loving eyes.
Joyful tears behind caring eyes.
Every lesson, softly told.
More precious now than crowns of gold.
Your gentle voice lights up my way,
guiding every three, a full day.
You're the anchor in the breeze,
the safe and gentle ease.
Oh, mother, your hands are my home.
Wherever I wonder, I'm never alone.
Your love is a river that joyfully flows.
A garden of dreams where
my whole life grows.
If I write, it's because you believe
every hope in my hope.
That you can see.
Oh, mother, no words can say.
How I thank you this mother's day.
If I could give the world to you,
it still wouldn't match all you do.
Every heart be joyfully praised.
May your life be filled with brighter
days.
Oh, Mom, your hands are my home.
Your love is the Joy, I've always known.
Through every season, come what may.
I'll carry your love every day.
Forever thankful, forever true.
The best for me comes from you.
Oh, mother, hear me say,
I love you more this mother's day.